<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
    <questions>
        <question>Eating a balanced diet is the most important factor for a healthy life. Explain your point of view.</question>
    </questions>
    <answers>
        <answer>&quot;We are what we eat.&quot;</answer>
        <answer>Everyone knows this sentence but yet our alimenation has never been so unhealthy.</answer>
        <answer/>
        <answer>Buying, cooking and eating an healthy food could appear like an impossible challenge and it is easier to eat prepared meals but this food contains a lot of fat and sugar which can have desastring impacts on our health at the long term. People who don't have a balanced diet say they don't have any time, not enough money or any cooking skills. Let's see if these reasons are good or not.</answer>
        <answer/>
        <answer>Eating a good and balanced food is not expensive. In fact, it's even less expensive than buying prepared meals. Making is own food in the garden is barely free and buying food in local of organic farms could cost more money but the quality of the products is far more higher.</answer>
        <answer/>
        <answer>Now everybody can cook. On internet you find pieces of advice, videos and forums where you can learn how to cook everything. Isn't a dream to taste a home-made bread, vegetables or even an home-made cheese ! Learning how to cook all these products is possible for everyone !</answer>
        <answer/>
        <answer>Cooking is own meal takes time but what are you doing when you put your pizza in the oven ? What are you doing when your fishsticks are in the microwave ? We save time when we eat prepared meals but does this saved time really useful ? Making is own food is a social, funny and calming activity which is the best way to end a hard day of work.</answer>
        <answer/>
        <answer>In conclusion, there is no real reason to eat prepared and fast food. You can now cook for you, your friends and your family a healthy, delicious and home-made food.</answer>
    </answers>
</root>
